fieldstonsoftware.com 2019-12-24

# Fieldston Software

  1. Home
  2. Company
  3. Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Statement (updated March 18th, 2019)

At Fieldston Software we take security of your data very seriously and your right to privacy is one of our primary concerns. This Privacy Policy describes the guidelines we use to protect the information we collect about you during your visit to our web site, our support site, and from our software. 

##### What information do we collect?

  * **Purchases and Subscriptions** \- We collect information relevant to the purchase including your name, email address, and street address. Fieldston Software uses an external payment processor (Paypal) for credit cards, so although you pay with a card, our systems store only the last four digits for tracking purposes. 
  * **Browser History** \- As you browse our website, anonymized analytics information is shared with Google Analytics, which is standard industry practice.
  * **Diagnostic Information** \- During troubleshooting or support we may ask you to send us logging or databases. These logs contain behavioral information on what our software did in an audit-trail fashion to allow us to determine errors in logic or how we handle specific points of data. In some cases we may ask for databases to be able to test issues we cannot reproduce. These logs will also contain raw descriptions of database fields that include event, task, note information from your database. 
  * **Licensing** \- Periodically our software will report to our servers the status of the license used. This information is used to ensure a license does not exceed the maximum allowed activations. 

##### How do we use the information?

The information we collect is strictly used for order processing, license management and advertising analytics. Information provided for troubleshooting and support purposes such as logs and databases are deleted locally from machines after being used to solve the problem. This content may remain on our Google hosted email account as allowed by Google policies. If you do not desire for Fieldston Software to access private information in these logs but you do require support, you may edit the log file directly using a text editor to remove private information before sending it to us. 

##### What information do we share?

Feldston Software will not use, rent, or sell ANY of your personal information for ANY reason other than to process your order request. Fieldston Software will not use ANY personal information for solicitations or junk email of any kind. 

##### Personal data used for syncing with gSyncit.

gSyncit requires access to your personal information for purposes of syncng your calendars, contacts, tasks and notes. All information is stored exclusively in Outlook or your local computer and exchanged with selected hosted services using a secured connection between your computer and that service. gSyncit maintains a locally cached copy of some of your content that remains on your local computer and used for software performance purposes. Fieldston Software does not have direct access to the personal information managed in Outlook, stored on your local computer, or within the services supported by gSyncit. 

##### Disclosure of the manner in which our application (gSyncit) accesses, uses, stores, or shares Google user data.

gSyncit accesses your Google account for purposes of exchanging information with Outlook in order to perform synchronization tasks. To initiate this process the user explicitly authorizes gSyncit to access their Google account where Google then issues a authorization token used for subsequent requests against the Google account. The Google account authorization token is stored locally on your computer along with all other personal information related to the purposes of syncing your data. Your personal information is never transmitted outside the scope of the secured connection between Outlook and Google services. We do not share or have access to any of your personal information. All locally cached information is for the sole purpose of syncing and serves no other purpose. 

##### Concent

Your consent, by visiting and purchasing products through the Fieldston Software website, to the collection and use of the information described above by Fieldston Software. We may periodically modify our privacy policy and will post any changes on this page so you can always be up to date on the information we collect and how we use it. We reserve the right to update this policy, and will notify you when we do. 

* * *
